bettyconfidential.com 2011-03-21

# Privacy Policy | BettyConfidential.com

BettyConfidential.com is an online service that allows each of its members to set up a unique personal profile, which can be linked with a network of friends. BettyConfidential.com members can view a portion of each other.s profiles and meet new friends using this service. To allow for new connections and friendships to be made, we display some personal information to other members. BettyConfidential.com members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them.

BettyConfidential.com cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at service@BettyConfidential.com.

**Your Account**

If you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password.

  **Information Collection and Use**

BettyConfidential.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users who enroll as members and to send notifications to those users relating to the BettyConfidential.com service. BettyConfidential.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, education, and occupation in order to assist our members in finding and communicating with each other. BettyConfidential.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate data, and browser type from members and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage, and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes only.

Member profile information is displayed to people in order to facilitate member interaction in the social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends and to send notifications related to the service. Members communicate with each other through the BettyConfidential.com service without disclosing their email addresses. Members' full names are never directly revealed to other members.

We may also use a member's email address to send updates, a newsletter, or other news regarding the service. Members may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "Subscription" settings.

From time to time, BettyConfidential.com or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest. To participate in the partner.s promotion, members may be asked to provide personal information including their name, email address, home address, or other information. If you provide this information, you agree to authorize BettyConfidential.com to transfer this personal information to the identified partner(s) from which you have explicitly requested to receive information. BettyConfidential.com will not be responsible for the partner's subsequent use of your personal information.

**Guidelines regarding children**

Personal information about children is a concern for all of us. At BettyConfidential, we take the protection of children's privacy very seriously. BettyConfidential does not encourage participation or visitation by children. BettyConfidential contains non-children’s content and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. Visitors who are known to be under the age of 13 are prohibited from becoming a member or subscriber. Anyone under the age of eighteen is discouraged from participating in any sex related chats or message boards and we ask that no one less than eighteen years of age become a community member.

BettyConfidential may at times sell products for children, but it sells them to adults, who can purchase with a credit card or other permitted payment method. If you are under 18, you may use BettyConfidential.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian. BettyConfidential reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel orders in their sole discretion.

  **Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members**

BettyConfidential.com members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. BettyConfidential.com stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friends list of the member sending the invitations and also to send reminders of the invitations. BettyConfidential.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders.

**Use of Cookies**

BettyConfidential.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences, to record session information for the purposes of ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements, and to customize newsletters, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and member profile information. You must enable cookies from BettyConfidential.com in order to use most functions on the site.

**Links**

BettyConfidential.com contains links to other sites. BettyConfidential.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on BettyConfidential.com.

**Public Forums**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds, or any other Public Forum including those in the social networking system found on BettyConfidential.com, information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**Third Party Advertising**

Advertisements appearing on this website may be delivered to visitors and members by BettyConfidential.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow their ad servers to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by BettyConfidential.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies (opt-out), [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Security**

BettyConfidential.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. BettyConfidential.com takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, including restricting access to member information to certain employees such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, BettyConfidential.com will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process received by BettyConfidential.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the BettyConfidential.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. BettyConfidential.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor-in-interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of BettyConfidential.com or substantially all of its assets to that successor-in-interest.

**Changes To the Privacy Policy**

From time to time, changes may be made to the privacy policy. If changes are made, they will be posted to make visitors and members aware of the changes. A visitor or member is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.

**Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at: service@BettyConfidential.com. Thank you.

* * *
